spyhunter.com 2011-12-30

# Privacy Policy « Remove Spyware & Malware with SpyHunter - Enigma Software Group USA LLC

Enigma Software Group USA, LLC, 2643 Gulf to Bay Boulevard, Suite 1560 #446, Clearwater, FL 33759, USA ("ESG") is dedicated to establishing a trusting relationships with its users, based on respect for personal identity and information, by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers all Web properties owned and maintained by ESG, including but not limited to www.enigmasoftware.com. We want to demonstrate its commitment to our users’ privacy and establish our users’ trust in our ability to protect their data. Therefore, we are disclosing:

  1. What personally identifiable information ESG collects.
  2. How ESG uses the information.
  3. With whom ESG may share user information.
  4. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
  5. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under ESG control.
  6. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact ESG Customer Support.

### Information Collection and Use

ESG is the sole owner of the information collected on its web properties, including www.enigmasoftware.com. ESG collects information from its users at several different points on our Web sites in accordance with the applicable data protection laws and strictly for the purposes necessary to our business and its users’ convenience. 

### Registration

In order to use ESG services at any level, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and email address), and a unique identifier. We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which the user has expressed interest. 

### Order

When a user purchases a paying service, we request information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and billing address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user. 

### Information Use

Subject to the legal exceptions listed in the Privacy Policy, ESG will not disclose to third parties the email addresses uploaded to our Web sites by our users for the purpose of using ESG products or services. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. For the session cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. It does not contain user’s personal data but only a specifically generated ID number and session ID. 

By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in with a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. Additionally, we use cookies for tracking purchases, conversions and distributing commissions to our affiliates. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by ESG Web properties only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Log Files

Like most Web sites, our servers use log files to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses stored in our servers for technical reasons are deleted automatically on a daily basis. 

### Service Announcements

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. These communications are not promotional in nature. 

### Customer Service

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and regarding issues relating to their accounts. We reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes. 

### Spam

ESG has a zero tolerance policy for abuse. 

### Sharing

#### Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. For example, ESG may disclose personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or third parties in response to criminal or civil subpoenas. 

### Third Party Intermediaries

We use an outside credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

### Business Transitions

In the event ESG goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the users’ personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given a choice not to have their information used in this different manner, as described in the notification of changes section, below. 

### Links

ESG’s Web sites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that ESG is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our sites and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by ESG’s Web sites. ESG has advertising and affiliate relationships with dozens of third party sites which drive interested parties to our sites. Information that is collected on these sites does not fall within the auspices of this policy. 

### Surveys

Periodically, our site may request information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of ESG’s services. Users’ personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys, they may not use customers’ personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

### Security

ESG takes every precaution to protect its users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via ESG’s Web sites, their information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order forms ask users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption protocol in the industry – SSL. While on a secure page, such as our paid order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just ’surfing’. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also employ security measures to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerks or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment. 

### Supplementation of Information 

In order for ESG to properly fulfill its obligations to users it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources. ESG verifies the billing address on all credit card transactions and may obtain credit reports for some corporate customers. The information obtained from these third party sources is maintained in a manner consistent with ESG’s Privacy Policy. 

### Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ personally identifiable information. 

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes in this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate, so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. 

### Contact Information

If you have any concerns about privacy at enigmasoftware.com, please fill out the privacy policy inquiries form with a thorough description and we will try to resolve it, or you can contact us at: 

**Enigma Software Group USA, LLC.  
Attn: Customer Service Department**  
2643 Gulf to Bay Blvd.  
Suite 1560 #446  
Clearwater, FL 33759  
USA
